Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
PHYSICAL: ASIA
10. CHARGE
The fourth quest.
The Death Match.
The 1,200-kg pillar push.
The first 2 countries
to complete 100 laps will survive.
The third and last country
will be eliminated immediately.
It's a test of perseverance.
Yeah, it's about perseverance.
Stand by.
Come on!
Gripping too high will make it harder.
-Okay.
-Place your grip in the middle.
We're not stopping, no matter what.
We'll find a way to keep pushing
in any way we can.
Outlast everyone!
100 laps!
Don't quit!
-Come on, we can do this.
-This is my shit.
I can do this forever.
I f****** live here.
We need to make sure
that we're walking in sync.
What's their plan?
Their stance doesn't look right.
Ready…
All right, here we go.
Like chilling.
Just keep pushing.
-Easy, guys. Let's go.
-Just keep that pace.
The pillar was easier to move
than I thought it would be.
But 100 laps?
Oh, this was gonna be brutal.
Hands out, head on.
Just keep walking, keep churning,
no matter what.
I knew this was gonna be a long haul.
-Really good, Dom. Come on, drive, drive!
-Beautiful!
-Hold that, now.
-Hold it!
Don't use your shoulders, guys.
Drive from your legs.
The weight of the pillar threw me off.
We had to put our entire weight into it.
I was so glad to have Min-jae.
Without him, we would've been screwed.
I wouldn't say it was light,
but it wasn't impossible to push either.
The pillar required
a decent amount of effort to move.
I wondered how we'd ever finish 100 laps.
We'd get exhausted in no time.
Push with your arms straight.
Min-jae, straighten your arms. That's it.
Looking good!
That's it. Hold that pace.
There we go.
Let's keep going.
Keep it going.
Team Mongolia
looks like they're on a stroll.
They're so slow.
-They're not even pushing.
-They're not.
They're just leaning forward against it.
This is good.
Team Mongolia's technique
is kind of unique.
-Why aren't they pushing?
-I don't know.
It was our way of conserving energy
while ensuring we were
all pushing with equal force
and going at the same pace.
This is good. No need to go faster.
We went slow and steady,
as there was no point in burning out soon.
Coming up on number one now.
Mongolia's struggling.
Let's go. That's one!
Team Australia's done one lap.
We're actually gonna be
ahead of Korea after this.
-Team Australia's ahead of us.
-It's fine.
We're in second place.
Team Australia's pretty fast.
Together. That's it.
Lock in like that.
Yeah, good, girls.
-Just keep that pace.
-Yeah.
Don't try and rush.
Beautiful, Dom! Great speed!
Korea's gassed.
Keep it moving.
Let's keep at it for second place.
We need at least second.
Min-jae, keep switching up your form.
-Okay.
-Good.
We tried different positions,
even using our shoulders to push.
-Doing great, Min-jae.
-Try using your head for leverage.
-Push a bit harder, Min-jae.
-Okay.
That's it.
See how much faster we're moving?
-That's it.
-Nice.
Our team's sped up.
-Team Korea's taken the lead.
-They have.
Team Mongolia isn't looking so good.
They're already lagging by half a lap.
Mongolia's gone.
Let's go. We're good.
This is a marathon!
Long haul. All day. Let's go!
Just nice and steady.
That's it.
Why don't you guys
push with your arms out?
No? That's how those guys are doing it.
There's no rush, right?
No, we're good.
Let's keep it like this.
We didn't rush at all.
This was a 100-lap marathon, after all.
We stuck to our plan
of going slow and steady.
We kept a steady pace
and distributed our force evenly.
We just focused on
keeping in step with one another.
You two are crushing it.
Don't let yourselves get burnt out.
Pace yourselves,
because we're going all out
in the last 50.
Ten.
We've done one tenth.
We're in the lead.
Time was passing so slowly.
I couldn't believe we had to do 100 laps.
Man, it felt like
some kind of
eternal wheel-turning punishment.
All right, that's 12!
Let's hold this pace.
We've still got 88 to go.
Was it ever going to end?
Even doing just two laps
felt like an eternity.
It was brutal.
The pillar weighed the same,
but the longer we went on for,
the heavier it felt.
Man, this is heavy.
No, you're doing great, Min-jae.
-Come on, Min-jae.
-Go, Min-jae!
You're killing it.
Pace yourselves.
Right, that's 20.
-What?
-Twenty.
Seriously?
-That's it?
-Yeah.
Damn, who came up with this?
This thing's so damn heavy.
Isn't 100 laps insane?
Of course it is.
I can't imagine having to do this myself.
Korea's gone, guys.
Let's go. Let's get them.
They're gassed.
Just getting warmed up.
Honestly, it's really tough out there.
I don't know how many laps.
My legs started to go numb.
My ankles were seizing up and locking up,
stepping in the sand.
It was tough.
Shorter steps!
Go, Alex. Come on!
I can't really get the shorter steps
because I'm right on this f****** hill.
I've got a new sand mountain
every time I come around
because of where the ball is,
so I can't even feel one of my legs.
I have that out-of-body experience.
It's pure torture all over again.
Alex, lean into Kate.
Alex, get right across.
I can't!
F*** off.
The wider you go,
the more torque we get, Kate.
So shift over into Dom's lane if you can.
Everyone, take a little shift.
I can't!
Don't worry about them.
Just do your thing, girl.
We're f****** locked in.
Yellow's gassed out!
Team Australia's gassed out.
Let's step it up a bit now.
-Let's step it up a bit now.
-Right, speed up.
-That's it, Orkhonbayar!
-Way to go, Mongolia!
-Way to go!
-You're doing great!
-That's what I'm talking about!
-That's it!
Yes, that's it! Keep that pace!
That's exactly it, guys!
They're picking up their rate.
You've got to pick up the rate!
-Need more speed. Let's go!
-Need more speed. You can't slow down!
Mongolia's catching us, Dom. Let's go!
Stay in front of them!
Charge through!
We need you guys to pick it up!
One, two. One, two.
Those guys have picked up their pace!
Come on, a little faster!
Let's push with our hands to go faster.
It's easier to push by hand.
Two. One, two.
We're pulling ahead! All right!
Keep that pace, guys!
Mongolia's jumping us, guys.
Come on, you've got to dig deep.
Find something.
Good shit, guys.
We just keep churning.
We got the engine for this.
Consistency's gonna win us.
Keep breathing.
You've gained another half lap!
Team Mongolia's speeding up!
How many laps do they have on us?
Two laps!
I glanced over and noticed
that no one was taking any breaks.
Let's take bigger steps.
Come on.
-Speed it up!
-Straighten those arms, everyone!
I thought, "Why is everyone so fast?"
Not a single team was pausing.
Come on. Damn it.
We couldn't let them catch up to us,
so I wanted to stay
at least five laps ahead.
If we get knocked out here,
we'll regret not going all out.
We need to give it everything we've got.
Let's go!
-Let's go!
I reasoned that l was already in hell,
which meant that nothing could
possibly make this worse.
I figured I might as well keep grinding.
We can rest when we're dead.
-Holy shit, man.
-I'll rest in my grave.
I'll save it for the grave too.
You've got to drive, or we're going home!
Come on, Mongolia!
All right!
We're getting there. The end's in sight.
It's just around the corner.
Let's just keep moving.
The interim score
will be revealed shortly.
Team Republic of Korea, 50 laps.
We're at 50, right?
We're in the lead!
There's no way they can match our speed.
We've got to catch up!
We should go one ahead.
Come on.
Yes, come on.
We kind of just discounted Korea
because we knew
that they would probably be ahead of us,
but with Mongolia,
they weren't an issue at all.
Doing 100 laps was way harder
than I thought it would be.
I'm sure it was worse
for Khandsuren and Adiyasuren.
I could feel that Khandsuren
was running out of gas,
which meant I had to shoulder
more of the burden.
Khandsuren, push.
I am pushing.
Being on the inside,
it was hard to keep in step
with the other two
because I was walking
with a bit of a stagger.
They're slowing down again.
-Push it, guys!
-Keep pushing!
Keep going, Khandsuren!
-One.
-Two.
Let's go, guys!
We've got to catch up, guys!
Time to catch up!
We've got to catch them now, guys!
F***.
Alex was really hurting,
so I was just trying to do
as much as I could to help.
We wanna give everything
to not be eliminated.
So we were just gonna give
absolutely everything and anything,
whatever it was gonna be.
We're strong.
We got guts.
Yes, Kate.
You're our secret weapon, Kate.
How can someone so light push like that?
-Right? She's a trooper for sure.
-She's an animal.
-She's insane.
-They've all got grit.
Yellow's catching up to us!
Team Australia's catching up!
There we go. That's it!
Team Australia's on your tail!
You can't let them catch you!
Let's push.
One, two. One, two.
They're quitting first!
As long as you don't stop!
Ready? I'll give a little bit more.
You guys, just hold your feet.
Thanks, Kate.
That speed. We need that!
Dark places!
Let's not slow down. Come on.
Nothing!
The Australian girls
were way beyond my expectations.
I thought we'd beat them easily,
but they were outperforming
and holding up really well.
It was a close match.
-It's neck and neck, right?
-Yeah, it is.
Team Australia's overtaken them!
-Yeah, good! Pick up the speed.
-That's great!
We're falling behind.
You're about three steps behind!
Come on.
One, two.
That's it. It'll be over soon.
Come on, kick it up a notch!
Mongolia's wavering, Dom!
Come on, don't waver, bro!
Come on.
We didn't f****** come all this way.
Let's link up.
Come on, girls.
Show them what we're made of.
-Leave it all here!
-They're hurting more than you!
No regrets!
Use every bit of energy!
They're moving in unison.
It's neck and neck.
Of course we were nervous.
Team Australia was much tougher
than I expected.
Probably one of the hardest events
I've ever actually seen
in anything that I've ever come across.
This is an insane match.
Dig deep!
Let's keep pulling ahead.
We've got to win this.
Let's go!
That's it!
Good stuff!
You've got to raise it together.
Just keep doing what you're doing!
Wow, shit!
I shouldn't have sworn
around my much older teammates.
But with the crushing weight,
the burning in my legs,
and the sand in my mouth,
I just couldn't help it.
Go, Min-jae!
-Go, Amotti! Go, Dong-hyun!
-You're almost there!
We're strong.
It's a mental game now.
Tell yourselves this is nothing.
That's good.
We got this.
I could even do 200.
-Are we at 80 by now?
-We're coming up to 80.
Okay. It'll get easier once we hit 90.
-A new me will be taking over at 90.
-Yeah.
-We just need to hold out till 90.
-Exactly.
Our goal is 90.
Someone else will do the rest.
-Wow, so fast!
-Way to go!
-Unbelievable.
-Check out the speed.
Let's go, South Korea!
That's it! Keep yelling!
You got this!
100 laps is inhumane.
It's insane.
It looks like pure hell.
Pick it up! Come on!
Pace, now! You've got to pick up the pace!
Temporary pain, Australia!
We're not going home here. Come on!
I need some speed, guys!
Alex, come on.
When are you gonna make the call?
We've got to go for it!
Team Australia's drained!
Come on, another push.
Nice, guys!
That's right, keep that pace!
Come on, guys!
They're picking up their rate!
You've got to pick up the rate!
I'm pretty spent, but I'll keep going.
-I'm pushing as hard.
-Yeah.
Thanks, Kate.
I was blown away by every so often,
Kate would just
churn in and push that thing
a little bit faster.
Dom, take over.
And it was just about taking turns
and really working as a unit
the whole way through,
and I couldn't be more proud of the girls.
-We have to go! Go, go!
-We've got to catch them, guys!
Come on, we're behind!
We've got to catch up!
We've got to dig in!
We got this.
It's not just about physical endurance,
it's about mental endurance.
Putting one foot in front of the other.
Continually. Do not stop.
Literally, the only way I'm stopping
is if it's over, the game's over,
or I'm literally dead.
Let's just keep going. One step.
F*** everyone else.
We know what we're doing.
This is the Death Match, guys!
There's nothing else after this!
Nothing else after this!
It was tough to keep going.
Turning a 1.2-ton pillar
100 times was tough.
Also, since the metal weights
were being dragged over sand,
the friction made it even more grueling.
I thought, "Why 100 laps?
Surely 50 would've been enough."
My two teammates
were completely spent too.
The worst was after we hit 50 laps,
because that's when the exhaustion
really hit me.
Everyone's hurting just as bad!
I was gasping for breath
and running on fumes.
I had nothing left in the tank.
My throat was bone dry.
They're slowing down! That's good!
We've got to catch them!
Come on, push!
Keep that pace!
We've got to catch up a lap!
Dom, got to jump!
Mongolia's just stopped, Dom!
-Let's go!
-Mongolia's stopped!
Kate, you reckon
you're sure you wanna do another burst?
Yeah, but I'd just die.
-Yeah.
-You still need to help me though.
There we go.
F***.
I'm pushing, I promise.
Come on! Don't stop!
Don't stop! Keep going!
Push!
-Let's keep pushing forward.
-All right.
-You're doing great, Khandsuren.
-Thanks.
Doing great, Orkhonbayar.
I'm not giving up.
I'm right here with you.
It's over soon.
Ninety.
Last ten laps!
-You're killing it!
-That's it, great pace! Keep it up!
We're on a roll!
Damn, Min-jae!
-Giant Baby!
-Go, Giant Baby!
Knowing it was the homestretch
motivated me to go faster.
The toughest stretch
was the final ten laps.
It was brutal.
It literally felt like
I was pushing a wall.
Man, this is killing me.
Come on, let's dominate them.
-Let's push on till the end.
-That's right.
This will be the last lap.
I might've miscounted by one,
so let's just keep going.
-Great stuff, guys!
-Amazing!
-That's it, Min-jae!
-Min-jae, your power really speeds it up!
You're absolutely killing it!
Let's do another lap.
One more, just in case.
-Our count must be off by one.
-Yeah.
I thought we'd hit 100 laps,
but the light wasn't coming on.
You never know.
Let's do one more.
Yeah, keep going.
Just keep going.
We might have one more to go.
This could be our last lap. Let's go!
I'd get my hopes up
that each lap was the last,
only to feel my heart sink
as I crossed the starting point.
The light just refused to come on.
I thought, "What's going on?"
I couldn't believe
I'd miscalculated by that much.
How many left?
You're done.
-This really is the last one.
-Last one! This is it!
Let's go, guys.
Push it like it's our last.
You're doing great, Min-jae.
-It's over.
-Republic of Korea, safe from elimination.
That's it, that's it.
-Great job, guys!
-Nice!
We made it.
Our strategy was a success.
Despite being ahead,
we didn't let our guard down
and gave it our all.
That was such a great feeling.
We were unshackled
and bathed in a bright light.
It really felt like
we'd escaped from hell.
We were truly free.
Damn, the soles of my feet are shot.
The pain was so intense,
it was truly the worst of my life.
Yeah, it was tough.
We were determined to keep going
and didn't stop even once.
My body gave out afterward.
Let's go! We made it!
Our plan worked.
Great job!
They finished so fast.
Good job!
-Korea's finished their 100 laps!
-Korea's done 100 laps!
A team had actually finished
their 100 laps.
That meant we were nearing it too.
It was time to dig deep
for the final push.
One.
You don't run, we're going home!
-You've got to run!
-Your engines are gonna beat theirs.
-Keep going.
-Come on, Kate!
Let's go, Dom. Dom, you've got to run!
Last pump.
I need you guys to catch up!
Come on. We're nearly finished.
-Let's go, come on.
-Yeah.
Team Australia's firing up.
-They're catching up to you!
-They're surging!
Team Australia's picking up speed.
Judo power!
Let's go!
They're speeding up.
-Should we push?
-Let's push.
Don't slow down! You've got to go!
We're almost there. Push through.
Speed finish!
They're slowing down!
Let's go, team! Speed!
Go, Australia!
Come on!
We didn't push 100 laps for this. Come on!
We didn't push f****** 100 laps to lose.
Come on!
Go!
Push, push!
We're going to win this Death Match,
no matter what.
I won't stop, no matter how tough it gets.
Let's clinch this, guys.
Come on, push.
We've got to do whatever it takes.
We're not going to give Team Australia
a shot at winning this.
Come on.
Who wants it more?
We do!
We don't wanna go home!
Come on, speed it up!
Last little push, guys.
You're amazing.
I'm trying to leverage.
Redlining, pushing 100%,
doing everything we can.
Putting our blood,
sweat, and tears into this.
My hair was everywhere, I was disheveled,
I was salivating, I was dripping in sweat.
Yeah, fully exhausted,
but I wasn't gonna miss the opportunity
to give everything I had
to this challenge.
Come on.
Don't stop.
Never.
Come on, light.
-Come on, light.
-Come on, give us the light.
-Come on.
-Give us the light.
Come on, guys! Give me more!
You're almost there!
Almost there!
You two are doing great.
I'm going to keep going too.
You're doing great. Hang in there.
The light's going to come on!
Just a little more! Keep pushing!
Come on, come on.
Keep going.
Push, guys!
Keep that speed!
Keep going, Australia. Come on!
Almost there, guys! Come on, final push!
Push through!
Do not stop!
Team Mongolia, safe from elimination.
Good job, you two.
Good job.
-They really went all out.
-They're crying. That's so cute.
They're completely spent.
They gave it everything.
They were tears of joy.
Beating a tough opponent like that
really boosted my confidence
in myself and my team.
We actually made it.
I was unbelievably happy.
I was just happy I never had to push
that damn thing again.
Hey, why don't you girls lie down?
There you go.
-F***!
-F***.
F***.
The pure exhaustion and emotional fatigue
just collapses you.
It sucked, honestly.
Because like, we're eliminated.
We're out of the competition.
And three of your members
who would kill to be in this game…
I guess I feel like
you've let them down as well.
You kind of can't believe
that you've been eliminated.
It's all right, guys.
-So bloody proud of you guys.
-Great effort!
Great effort, guys.
Good effort, guys.
It sucks.
My pride is definitely hurt,
just not being able to
finish the challenge,
but I was really proud of my teammates.
And yeah, we gave it everything we could.
It's the name of the game.
We're one of the strongest,
if not the strongest, team here,
so we did not expect
to be eliminated today.
Oh god, here we go.
Great heart, guys.
-I'm sorry, bro.
-No, don't be silly.
Don't be sorry, bro.
F****** gangster for this.
We did it, babe.
We represented Australia well.
They gave everything they had,
I am so sure.
They gave everything they had.
Some days aren't yours.
Physical: Asia.
The country being eliminated
from the fourth quest is…
Team Australia.
They're a loaded team.
It goes to show how one bad call
is enough to take you out.
You can't just bank on one thing.
I can't believe
they just took out these guys.
I know.
My team gave everything they had,
and I'm proud of them.
And I know Australia will be as well.
I've grown a lot from this experience,
and I'm grateful for the opportunity.
Always leading by example.
"O Captain! My Captain!"
Leading from the front,
as always, skipper.
I am so grateful to be
a part of this amazing team
and also surrounded
by these other amazing athletes.
Thank you for such an amazing event.
We'll go out with a bang.
He never loses his positive attitude.
I'm a bit sad to see him go.
I'm so proud of our team.
We put blood, sweat, and tears into this.
I've made lifelong friends here.
I love them to bits.
Bring us back next season,
and let's see what happens.
What an experience.
Super grateful for the opportunity.
Super grateful.
I think there were a lot of cool,
memorable moments during this experience.
Doing the ship challenge
collectively as a team
was definitely one of the highest points.
We were so new to each other still,
but we came together
to form a real, true team.
You know, I had planned to win this
and then move into my K-pop career,
but I think I'm gonna have to
go back to fighting.
I thought that I was gonna be
more sad, destroying my torso,
but we went out the way we came in,
with big smiles and a lot of laughter.
This team has just been incredible,
and without them,
I wouldn't have been able to push past
every physical and mental barrier
that I have.
-Aussie, Aussie, Aussie!
-Oi, Oi, Oi!
-Aussie!
-Oi!
-Aussie, Aussie, Aussie!
-Oi, oi, oi!
Oh god.
Man…
It's unfortunate that it has to
kind of end like this,
but we still definitely wholeheartedly
believe that we're the best team here.
So it's quite sad to be having to leave.
It was an honor representing Australia
at Physical: Asia.
We're gonna dominate the world
next time we do this.
Let's do it.
When I say "cattle," you say "dog"!
-Cattle!
-Dog!
That is strong.
I'm keeping that till the end.
Here are the surviving countries so far
in Physical: Asia.
We Japan…
are a phoenix.
Even when it looked like
we were down and out,
we rose from the ashes.
The shipwreck transportation match.
The winning team is
Team Australia.
We don't ever give up.
And then there was the Death Match.
The surviving country is
Team Japan.
We had a rough start.
-But we're on a roll now.
-Yeah, we've got momentum.
The battle rope relay.
The country in first place is Japan.
We've made it this far,
and we're going to win.
-One, two, three!
-Go, Japan!
The Mongolians are a nation of warriors.
Warriors!
-Mount up!
Our great teamwork
through the first four quests
is what's got us this far.
Get up here!
We Mongolians
have outstanding strength,
and we have warrior blood in our veins.
Losing is not our thing.
Forget the top three, we're here to win.
Warriors!
-Mount up!
The shipwreck transportation match.
The winning team is
Team Republic of Korea.
Our team is defined by
our willpower and perseverance.
We can do this!
If we just keep doing what we're doing,
victory is guaranteed.
Keep your head!
The surviving country is
Republic of Korea.
We're winning this, no matter what.
-Republic of Korea!
-Let's go!
Physical strength stems from the mind.
Let us show you how strong we are.
Congratulations on making it through
the fierce competition.
Contestants, please enter the hall.
-What's this now?
-What's this?
What's that?
What's this?
They're some kind of chairs.
-Goodness, what's going on here?
-What is this?
They look like electric chairs.
Physical: Asia.
Just hearing his voice
gives me the chills now.
I'm actually kind of nervous.
The fifth quest will now begin.
Quest five, here? You mean right now?
I think we're going straight into it.
All the refs are here too.
Hey, stop it.
This freaks me out every single time.
Those two are fine, but we girls
are having a nervous breakdown.
My heart can't take this.
Before that, we will proceed
with a pre-quest mission
that grants a special privilege
for survival in the fifth quest.
It's a pre-quest mission
before the fifth quest.
A privilege like that
can make all the difference
in Physical: Asia.
So winning this was crucial.
The pre-quest mission
of Physical: Asia is…
-Here it comes.
-Damn.
The pre-quest mission is…
the manual treadmill relay.
I did not see that coming.
Damn, not the treadmill.
-A relay?
A relay?
A relay was the last thing I expected.
For the manual treadmill relay,
each country will select one male
and one female contestant.
Oh, what? Just two?
The two contestants
will take turns running
on a manual treadmill.
The number of switches allowed is…
Okay, hit us with it.
The number of switches allowed is
unlimited.
…unlimited.
-Unlimited?
That's a game-winner.
We can switch as many times as we want.
The game will last for three minutes.
The country that covers
the greatest distance by the end wins.
Do you want to take this on, Sung-bin?
-Three minutes is too long for me.
-Is it?
Yeah, it's too long.
If it were three people running,
I'd definitely put myself in.
I'm honestly confident in this one myself.
But as the all-rounder,
I think this one's for you, Amotti.
Seung-yeon, have you trained on those?
Yes, I have.
Great, you can be our female player then.
Do we have a shot at crushing this?
Team Japan's too stacked though.
-Team Japan?
-Yeah, they are.
Stretch your legs a bit.
You can't just jump right into it.
This pre-quest could decide
whether we make it to the final or not.
In our team,
we have Hashimoto who's agile and strong,
with good balance.
And then there's Itoi
with explosive power.
It was a really tough call
between the two.
Who's our female player?
It was between Adiyasuren and me.
Given my height,
light weight, and longer legs,
we decided I'd be the one to run.
The male player wasn't as easy to pick,
and we had to hash it out a bit.
Now, all participants from each country,
please step up to your treadmills.
Republic of Korea!
-Let's go!
All right!
I was under a lot of pressure.
Losing this mission
would be a huge setback for the team,
so I had to make the privilege ours,
no matter what.
To be honest, I don't have it in me.
I don't have it in me to mess this up.
-One, two, three!
-Go, Japan!
Who are they sending?
Come on, let's see!
They're sending him in?
I thought it would be the judoka.
Is he any good at running?
I was the stolen base leader
in my baseball days,
so I'm confident in my running.
That's why I was picked for this mission.
I've always been a natural sprinter
when it comes to short distance,
so Itoi and I were chosen
as the runners for our team.
That guy is carrying his team on his back.
-The man is a machine.
-He is.
Itoi is obviously a tough opponent,
but the one who really worried me
was Mongolia's Enkh-Orgil.
MMA fighters have great stamina,
so I knew he'd be a strong runner.
You got this!
The pre-quest mission of Physical: Asia
with a powerful privilege on the line.
The manual treadmill relay will now begin.
I grew up in the countryside,
riding horses, climbing rocks,
and running up to the tops of mountains.
So this challenge is a piece of cake.
I'm ready to push past my limits
to win the privilege for my team.
I'm giving this everything I got
to win the privilege.
I need to do this for my team.
-Ready…
-All right.
Stay cool, man. You got this.
Looking good.
That's it. Nice pace!
That's good, that's good.
That's it! Open up those strides!
Good!
The plan was that
I'd handle the long sprints,
and Khandsuren would take over
in short bursts to give me a break.
Since we'd lose a bit of time
every time we switched,
we figured it'd be better
to switch as little as possible.
Come on, give it your all!
Don't exhaust yourselves!
All right!
Nice!
They're switching already?
One of the teams has switched runners!
Looking good!
Two and a half minutes!
Okay, 30 seconds.
Be ready to jump on quick! Keep it tight!
It's a technique I used a lot in training.
Short sprints and quick swaps
were imperative.
The longer you run, the slower you get.
There's no way around it.
So our plan was to switch
as soon as either of us started fading.
There was a privilege on the line.
I was desperate to win it for my team.
They're swapping again.
You can swap if you're fading!
Swap if you're gassing out!
Team Korea was switching
back and forth from the get-go.
They were doing it in short intervals,
almost every 20 seconds,
and I wondered
if that was the smarter move.
Swap players if you're losing steam!
Swap if you need to, okay?
-You're up.
-Got it.
-All right, go! Go, Nonoka, go!
-All right, go, Nonoka!
Yeah, kick it, girl! Stay balanced!
-Nice!
-All right!
Yeah, hold that pace!
Their plan must be to swap every minute.
They still haven't swapped.
I'm totally fired up
with the determination to win.
I'm giving it my everything
until my time is up.
Let's swap now!
Very nice!
Yeah, pump those arms! Go, girl!
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve…
Get ready!
Amotti's fast.
Yeah, he is.
The fast swaps kept it
quite manageable physically.
Swap out if you're fading!
I'm off!
Go! That's it, keep it tight!
Itoi, swap when you're losing steam!
Swap if you're wiped!
I saw how Team Korea was switching
and figured shorter bursts
might be better.
So two minutes into the game,
we changed our strategy to match theirs.
-You're on!
-Okay.
And that's how we continued,
swapping frequently.
That's it, that's it!
Jump off if you're wiped out!
There you go!
Right on! You're dialed in now!
Come on, crank it up!
-You're crushing it! Pace it now!
-You can pace yourselves.
I just went full throttle.
I ran, but with pure desperation.
I just did my best.
You can pace yourself.
The breaks were always over too soon.
I felt fine at first,
but after a few cycles,
I could feel myself running out of gas.
Go, go!
You can jump off when you're cooked,
so go all out!
Yes, do short bursts!
Go full gas!
Only stay on while you're maxed!
-I'm off!
-Ten seconds, go!
Go, Itoi!
You can step it up now!
I focused on recovering quickly
after each stint.
And while I was sprinting,
I had to convince myself
that this was just a walk in the park.
That baseball guy is a beast.
He kills it at everything.
Don't overdo it!
-One minute!
-One minute.
One minute!
You're doing amazing!
Last minute!
-Swap now, swap now!
-Swap out!
There's no rush! Just keep going!
Hang tight, Itoi.
Go, Nonoka!
Go, go, go!
Push forward, push forward!
Push forward!
Itoi, take it to the end!
I got the last 30 seconds.
Hold till 30 seconds to go!
Forty seconds left! Push it, Nonoka!
Yes! We got this in the bag!
Swap out, swap out!
Let's go!
Try ten-second bursts, guys!
Move those legs!
Five more seconds! Come on!
-Go, go, go!
-Change players!
-Go!
-Go, go, go!
-Change players!
-Go!
By that point, I was absolutely toast,
but there was no way
I was going to lose this.
Thirty seconds.
Thirty!
Give him five seconds to catch his breath!
Khandsuren, take over!
Give him five seconds!
Come on, swap!
Yes!
That's it! Get that number up!
-Ten seconds! Final push!
-You're almost there!
You're almost there!
-Final push!
Swap out!
-This is it!
-This is the final stretch!
Last 20 seconds!
-Let's go!
-Go, go, go!
Swap if you need to! Go!
You're up!
Go, Nonoka!
-Push forward!
-Run for the last seconds!
Final stretch!
That's it, that's it!
-Swap now!
Don't check the time!
Exert your power!
Go on full send! Give it your all!
Ten seconds.
-Nine!
-Eight!
-Seven!
-Six!
Five!
Four! Three!
-Two!
-One!
-Game over.
-Man, that was wild!
Game over.
Solid fight, guys. That was insane.
Great job.
You did amazing, guys!
They're exhausted.
My legs are shot.
Yeah, mine are too. Great effort.
It was tough, really tough.
I could taste blood
in the back of my throat,
so I knew I'd pushed myself to the limit.
That was brutal.
Great job, you two.
I totally hit my limit at the end.
It was rough.
The running challenge
was the hardest so far.
The manual treadmill relay
of Physical: Asia.
The result will now be announced.
I was going too hard to look around.
Come on, Japan.
The third place will first be announced.
Come on.
The third place is…
Team Mongolia.
Just as I thought.
Good effort, Enkh-Orgil.
Good effort, guys.
Team Mongolia recorded 917 meters.
Solid effort, guys.
That was good teamwork.
The first place will now be announced.
Come on.
Japan.
Let it be Japan.
Come on. Please let it be Japan.
Team Republic of Korea.
I told you he'd be the happiest.
He's totally lost it.
You told us not to overreact.
-All right!
-You crushed it!
You completely dominated it!
Oh yeah, the score.
Team Republic of Korea
recorded 1,114 meters.
Team Japan recorded 1,024 meters.
-100 meters?
-They weren't far behind.
Running 100 meters
takes about 10 to 14 seconds.
So we were about twelve seconds apart.
That was close.
There was basically just
twelve seconds between us.
Team Republic of Korea wins the privilege
for the fifth quest.
Thank you guys!
That was all you.
It was all you.
Man, they saved our asses again.
Tough break.
-Let's aim for the next win.
-It is what it is.
-Hey, good effort.
-Good effort.
We suffered a crushing defeat.
But on a brighter note,
it wasn't an actual quest,
and we're not giving up.
Next time, the win is ours.
-You okay? How are your legs?
-We're fine.
-Are you good?
-Yeah.
-Great work, man.
-Thanks.
Seung-yeon, you killed it.
There was a huge edge on the line,
and I feel like
we gave it our all and did well,
so I'm proud.
Physical: Asia.
Now,
the fifth quest will be revealed.
Give it to us.
What's next?
The fifth quest is…
a record challenge.
-A record challenge?
A record?
Record what? Weight?
Or is it speed?
I have no clue.
In this record challenge,
the countries will perform the task
one by one.
One team at a time.
It's not a head-to-head this time.
So the fastest team advances.
I'm assuming it'd be the most similar
to the shipwreck match.
Of the three countries, two will survive,
while the lowest-ranked country
will be eliminated…
…will be eliminated immediately.
-No more Death Matches then.
-This is make-or-break.
Now, Team Republic of Korea's privilege
-will be revealed.
-Let's hear it.
Please make it good.
As the first-place winner
of the pre-quest mission…
Team Republic of Korea
may view the map for the fifth quest.
…may view the map for the fifth quest.
A map?
We get to see the map.
This is sweet.
Nice one.
It's a huge edge,
because we get to see the map
while the other teams have to fly blind.
A map?
It doesn't matter to us.
I don't think a map's
going to help them all that much.
I'm not sweating the fifth quest.
This win is ours.
We're sending either Team Japan
or Team Korea home.
You may now check the map.
Let's scope it out, guys.
-Don't let them peek.
-Huddle up.
So, about this map…
Over here.
Sorry.
-It's huge.
-Let's see.
-Is that a bridge?
-Keep it quiet, man.
-They don't speak Korean anyway.
-Oh, right, my bad.
Dong-hyun, sneak us a look.
What are they whispering?
What's on that thing?
Of course I was jealous.
That was the winner's perk.
I tried to sneak a peek like this.
I wanted to see
what Dong-hyun was holding.
Should we crash their little map party?
You're the team leader, so you go.
Just barge in and stick your head in.
We were just messing around.
What are those wooden sticks?
I guess we have to walk on them.
What are these then? Obstacles?
-They look like obstacles.
-Looks like it.
-We'll need to climb over them.
-Like this?
This is on the ground,
so we'll need to pull the rope to lift it.
Here's another one.
It think it works the same way.
Yeah, you might be right.
That's why there's a rope.
The point of reading the map
was to figure out what to do,
but the map didn't give that information,
so we could only speculate among ourselves
about what we'd be facing.
All contestants,
please make your way to the arena.
Physical: Asia.
Team Republic of Korea,
please enter the arena.
-Look, we were right. It's up there.
-Yeah.
This almost feels like a war zone.
-Right?
This is way bigger than I thought.
This is our cargo.
-I think we're hauling the whole thing.
-Yeah.
Maybe it's a military supply
transportation match.
Physical: Asia.
The fifth quest is
the castle conquest.
-The castle conquest?
-A conquest?
What's that?
It's a sand mound.
It was massive.
The map made things look smaller.
So I thought the castle, the wagon,
and everything would be small,
but the castle towered over us
and the wagon was massive.
I felt tiny in comparison.
The castle conquest is a record challenge
in which you will transport
a cargo wagon into the bailey.
This won't be easy.
The wagon looks heavy as hell.
It's loaded to the max.
The country that takes the longest
to conquer the castle will be…
eliminated immediately.
That's brutal.
Okay, I got the hang of it.
The fifth quest.
The castle conquest.
-Think of this as our last shot!
-Once the whistle blows,
-Man, I'm shaking.
-the match will begin.
-I'll take the closest one.
-Okay.
Stand by.
I was ready to crush it.
I was certain that we'd take this.
I had a good feeling about this one.
Ready…
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher